Se-no, Rattle Channel GOGO!
So, today's project is "Se-no, I'm going to introduce my memories!
As the name suggests, I'd like to introduce some of our memories from the past.
So, since I have four and Momo has three, I would like to introduce the first one.
I would like to introduce the first one.
This is a strap of a local Oni-no-Enme blade. It is a key chain.
Does that mean there are 47 of them?
No, there are not 47. But, you know, we often work in the countryside.
I'd like to buy one every time I go there.
Is that so?
And when we reported it to our fans, some of them gave them to us, and we collected one.
Wow, how many do you have now? By the way, how many do you have now?
How many do you have? But, you know, I think we can have 2 or 30 at least, can't we?
My favorite is Kanao-chan. A girl.
Kanao-chan.
This one?
Yes, that's right. And Kanao collected quite a lot. This is how I collected them.
By the way, what do you recommend?
Something that brings back memories.
So, something from your hometown.
Oh, local memories?
No, no, no. We used to buy them every time we went to the countryside, so I thought they were memories.
Sure, sure, sure.
We used to buy them when we just got back from a re-leave, so it's a memory.
It was a time when we were looking for them and buying them. It's very much Noya's time, so I was looking for something to buy.
Is it there? At a convenience store.
In a convenience store?
You mean it's in a convenience store? It's a local thing.
That's amazing.
The first one is this Oni-no-Kiri key chain.
I'm not that beautiful.
I'm not that little bit beautiful,
It's a pair of shoes, but I've had these for about 3 or 4 years now, maybe since I was in Osaka,
That's a lie,
When we moved here, my mother bought me matching sandals for the first time,
They are yellow for her and beige for me,
They were really dirty, but they were my favorite and I wore them all the time.
They were really dirty, but I loved them and wore them for a long time,
And last year, too,
I wore them last year when I was invited to perform at Izakaya Exile,
I remember that the staff and members worked very hard to reinforce them with tape on both sides because they said these pillars were dangerous,
I still continue to wear them.
I see. Well, thanks to the members and the staff, I can still wear them today, with all my heart.
That's right. That's right. So please reinforce them again this year.
I don't have any experience in reinforcement.
Kira-chan did it for me, so I'll ask Kira-chan to do it again.
Okay, Kira-san, please do that.
I would like to continue with the second question. I'll go on and on.
Okay, this way.
Yes, I'm the one from Sylvanian Family, with pride. Yes, I am, I am a Sylvanian Families thing, with pride.
Sylvanian Families.
I, eh, what were you the type to play with when you were little? You know, like Koeda-chan.
Rika-chan.
I had a big house. With a ping-pong chime.
Yes, yes, yes. I was a Sylvanian.
I already had two houses and a kindergarten.
This is a kindergarten bus.
I used it a lot, so I thought I could take it with me.
Oh, look.
What?
Look, there's something in it.
The driver's hat.
And a song. There's a song on it.
And it's a trampoline.
Who jumps on it?
No, the animals.
Oh, what?
Sylvanian animals fly.
If you put them on the trampoline and leave them alone, they will fly.
Well, I was thinking of a trampoline that you could turn into a trampoline by putting the animals in a container and then leaving it like this.
If you put the animals in the bin and leave them alone, will they just fly away?
No, it does not.
It's manual, of course.
Oh, you mean they play by themselves like this? Oh, you mean you play it this way and this way by yourself?
Manually, of course.
Amazing.
Animals don't move suddenly, do they?
By the way, if you pull this bus or release it, it will go "piyoon".
It doesn't move.
Yes, it doesn't.
Yes.
It's all manual.
It's difficult.
We were a surrealist family.
Well, I, you know, I really, you know, redecorated the other day,
I threw away all my old stuff, all my old stuff, and this is actually gum.
When I started this YouTube, I was asked to do an unannounced? When I started this YouTube, I think I did an unannounced bag check, but at that time, I had put it in a drop bag.
I did.
Gum.
It came out. Seriously?
We always do this at the same time.
I've been putting it in there for a long time.
I have a theory that it might be on my desk, but I probably threw it away.
Please throw it away.
I changed it to this about a year later.
I can't say anymore.
After that, I received a lot of letters from fans, about the thickness of this one. After that, a fan sent me a lot of Ziplocs
I got a lot of Ziplocs about this thick from a fan.
Why?
He told me to put gum in them.
Oh, I see.
Yes, I'm putting it in these right now.
I don't know what to say. I don't know what the right comment is.
But isn't it a memory?
What memories?
Memories from the beginning of YouTube.
There's more.
Go on.
Last one, Momochan, last one.
I'll be the third.
Yes, well, I'm Gilles Chart perfume.
Seriously, when I smell it at a concert.
I feel like it's the beginning of the show!
Yes, I bought it for the first time at our first show.
I bought it for the first time when we played our first show and I wanted to wear perfume at the show.
Vanilla is gone.
Yes, it's totally gone.
We always use this when we go to live shows, we used it for our first live show.
Wow, it smells like a live show!
I feel like I'm at a fan show or something.
So many things have been happening lately.
I've started using this perfume. I've started to use this kind of perfume.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
But...
I use this when I go to live shows.
Yes, when I shake this
When I do Yuzu
Oh, like the smell of yuzu
Yeah, it starts
You say, "The show is about to start.
This is the perfume of the beginning.
That's for sure.
No, but it really smells like that.
Manila.
That's right.
Okay, I'll go next to this bracelet.
Oh, yes.
She lives in England.
Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
A friend of mine...
Yes, a friend of mine lives in England.
I can usually get in touch with him on LINE or something like that, but...
but sometimes we exchange letters.
Heh...
This is the first present she gave me.
It has my initials "M" on it.
How cute! Eww, so cute!
Momoka's with flowers.
Here you go
It's so cute!
I see.
He put a flower on it because "Momoka" is the Chinese character for flower.
I see...
So... two English friends and two Japanese friends...
I was friends with all four of them.
But my British friend had all four of us wearing the same flower...
Hey!
He sent them to me, so I've been seeing them a little bit.
Looks amazing!
I take really good care of it so that I don't lose it or break it.
Thank you very much.
How did you do that?
It's not handmade.
Handmade?
I picked out some initials and a little something like that.
I see.
I can add this.
It's like a custom order.
Like a custom-made bracelet.
Yes, yes, yes, it's like a custom-made bracelet.
It's not correspondence, it's not correspondence, it's just old-fashioned correspondence Nice correspondence, not correspondence, a bit old fashioned.
Correspondence.
Well, in a way, it is correspondence, but not as often as it should be.
But how do you exchange letters... about England?
Why don't you just put it in the mailbox?
I'll go all the way to the post office and go through the formalities.
I don't know.
That's why I can't do it often.
That's right.
That's great.
Memories.
And last but not least... this girl.
Kuranosuke.
My name is Kuranosuke.
This is... my partner from Miracle Tunes.
He was my partner in Miracle Tunes, and he's my only partner.
We slept together back then.
Yes.
Yeah, but now he's just displayed where I can see him.
I miss this feeling.
I brought Kuranosuke because I thought this would be the most memorable.
When this whole thing started, Shiori Ayoka had a solo partner, but the other girls didn't.
But the other girls didn't have a partner.
I was a little bit jealous of them because they all had a partner like Mokonya.
But I'm also a little proud of myself. But I'm also a little proud of this.
I'm serious.
Only Maria Kruczynski and MiraChew would do that for each and every one of them.
Yeah.
I'm really jealous of Rhythms.
Thank you very much.
Chachamaru, I was actually going to name my dog Kuranosuke.
That's right.
I was going to, but Kuranosuke didn't suit my face.
You're right.
I thought "Maru" would be cuter, so we decided on "Chachamaru".
Well, I brought it here because it holds a lot of memories for me.
I've finished introducing him...
Are you okay with it?
How was it?
I wanted to bring something a little more used, but...
Maybe she just wanted to lighten her load.
No, she looked for it.
But it was after we decluttered.
I hope it's a good memory for you all.
I don't know how to be patient.
Of course you don't.
I don't know.
So, thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
Please leave a comment and click the "good button"! Best regards and good button comments please.
Bye bye!
See you soon!
I'm wearing d-holic's outfit this time!